New York StateWide Senior Action Council; Records apap111
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- Subject Files, 1974-1979; 1983-1999; 4; 9.58 cubic ft.
  - Health Care and Medicare, 1983-1998; 4.1; 6.79 cubic ft.
    - Mandatory Medicare Assignment Public Response, 1989 (Box 4 (4-Subject Files), Folder 36)
    - Massachusetts Health Care Legislation, 1987 (Box 4 (4-Subject Files), Folder 37)
    - "Medicaid: A Program Crucial to Women's Health", National Women's Law Center, ca. 1995 (Box 4 (4-Subject Files), Folder 38)
    - Medicaid Applications by County, 1989 (Box 4 (4-Subject Files), Folder 39)
    - Medicaid Application Guide, 1985 (Box 4 (4-Subject Files), Folder 40)
    - Medicaid, Bill 328, Home Care Provisions, 1996 (Box 4 (4-Subject Files), Folder 41)
    - Medicaid Block Grant, 1995 (Box 5 (4-Subject Files), Folder 1)
    - Medicaid Block Grant, Material, 1995 (Box 5 (4-Subject Files), Folder 2)
    - Medicaid Cuts, 1994-1995 (Box 5 (4-Subject Files), Folder 3)
    - Medicaid Cuts Action Group, Prospective Member List, Undated (Box 5 (4-Subject Files), Folder 4)
    - Medicaid Cuts, NYS Health Care Campaign, 1994 (Box 5 (4-Subject Files), Folder 5)
    - Medicaid Documentation Issues, 1983-1990 (Box 5 (4-Subject Files), Folder 6)
    - Medicaid, Entitlements and Advocacy Training, Brookdale Center on Aging, 1989 (Box 5 (4-Subject Files), Folder 7)
    - Medicaid, Entitlements and Advocacy Training, Brookdale Center on Aging, 1996 (Box 5 (4-Subject Files), Folder 8)
    - Medicaid Fraud, 1989; 1994 (Box 5 (4-Subject Files), Folder 9)
    - Medicaid, Hospital Information, 1990 (Box 5 (4-Subject Files), Folder 10)
    - Medicaid Information, Miscellaneous, 1989-1990 (Box 5 (4-Subject Files), Folder 11)
    - Medicaid Managed Care Alert, 1995 (Box 5 (4-Subject Files), Folder 12)
    - Medicaid, Managed Care Newsletters, 1997-1998 (Box 5 (4-Subject Files), Folder 13)
    - "Medicaid Program in NYS: An Advocate's Handbook", 1988 (Box 5 (4-Subject Files), Folder 14)
    - Medicaid Reform, 1988-1990 (Box 5 (4-Subject Files), Folder 15a-b)
    - Medicaid Restructuring, Bill 52, 1995 (Box 5 (4-Subject Files), Folder 16)
    - Medicaid Restructuring Proposal, 1987-1988 (Box 5 (4-Subject Files), Folder 17)
    - Medicaid Seminar, Koldin & Levine Law Center, 1990 (Box 5 (4-Subject Files), Folder 18)
    - Medicaid Takeover Legislation, 1992 (Box 5 (4-Subject Files), Folder 19)
    - Medicaid Workgroup, 1992-1993 (Box 5 (4-Subject Files), Folder 20)
    - Medicaid Workgroup Meeting, 1991-1992 (Box 5 (4-Subject Files), Folder 21)
    - Medical Care Fraud, Bill A.4689, 1993 (Box 5 (4-Subject Files), Folder 22)
    - Medical Payment Dispute Resolution Regulation (DRG), 1990 (Box 5 (4-Subject Files), Folder 23)
    - Medical Payment Dispute Resolution System, 1990-1991 (Box 5 (4-Subject Files), Folder 24a-b)
    - Medical Payment Dispute Resolution System, Request for Proposals to Implement, 1990 (Box 5 (4-Subject Files), Folder 25)
    - Medicare, Advocacy/Resolution, 1989-1991 (Box 5 (4-Subject Files), Folder 26)
    - Medicare and Medicaid, General Information, 1985-1986 (Box 5 (4-Subject Files), Folder 27)
    - "Medicare and Medicaid Guide", 1988 (Box 5 (4-Subject Files), Folder 28)
    - "Medicare and Medicaid Guide", Law and Legislation, 1987 (Box 5 (4-Subject Files), Folder 29)
    - "Medicare and Medicaid Guide", Supplemental Update, 1986 (Box 5 (4-Subject Files), Folder 30)
    - "Medicare and Medicaid Guide", Supplemental Update, 1989 (Box 5 (4-Subject Files), Folder 31)
    - Medicare Beneficiaries Defense Fund, 1992-1993 (Box 5 (4-Subject Files), Folder 32)
    - Medicare Billing Rates File, 1989 (Box 5 (4-Subject Files), Folder 33)
    - Medicare Bulletins, Brookdale Center on Aging, 1991 (Box 5 (4-Subject Files), Folder 34)
    - Medicare Catastrophic Protection Act, 1988-1989 (Box 6 (4-Subject Files), Folder 1)
    - Medicare Coalition Conference, 1997 (Box 6 (4-Subject Files), Folder 2)
    - Medicare Information, 1986-1988 (Box 6 (4-Subject Files), Folder 3)
    - Medicare Information, 1988-1990 (Box 6 (4-Subject Files), Folder 4)
    - Medicare Information, 1991-1992 (Box 6 (4-Subject Files), Folder 5)
    - Medicare Legislation, Balanced Billing, Bill A. 100, 1993 (Box 6 (4-Subject Files), Folder 6)
    - Medicare Legislation, Beneficiaries Protection Amendments, H.R. 1707,1995 (Box 6 (4-Subject Files), Folder 7)
    - Medicare Legislation, Cap on Physician Fees, Bill 12304, 1992 (Box 6 (4-Subject Files), Folder 8)
    - Medicare Legislative Issues, 1992 (Box 6 (4-Subject Files), Folder 9)
    - Medicare Marketing Guidelines, 1996 (Box 6 (4-Subject Files), Folder 10)
    - Medicare Reform Conference, 1996 (Box 6 (4-Subject Files), Folder 11)
    - Medicare Reform Draft Discussion Document, 1995 (Box 6 (4-Subject Files), Folder 12)
    - Medicare Workgroup, 1995 (Box 6 (4-Subject Files), Folder 13a-b)
    - Medigap Policies and Information, 1991; 1995 (Box 6 (4-Subject Files), Folder 14)
    - National Healthcare Campaign, Insurance Coverage Issues, 1989 (Box 6 (4-Subject Files), Folder 15)
    - National Senior Citizen's Law Center, Report on Nursing Home Issues, 1986 (Box 6 (4-Subject Files), Folder 16)
    - New Yorkers For Accessible Health Coverage (NYFAHC), Memos, 1994 (Box 6 (4-Subject Files), Folder 17)
    - Nursing Home Community Coalition Meetings, 1989-1991; 1993 (Box 6 (4-Subject Files), Folder 18)
    - Nursing Home Immunizations Report, 1994 (Box 6 (4-Subject Files), Folder 19)
    - Nursing Home Industry Report, 1994 (Box 6 (4-Subject Files), Folder 20)
    - Nursing Home Issues, 1990 (Box 6 (4-Subject Files), Folder 21)
    - Nursing Home Residents' Rights, 1983-1985; 1989 (Box 6 (4-Subject Files), Folder 22)
    - Nursing Home Residents' Rights and Issues, 1992 (Box 6 (4-Subject Files), Folder 23)
    - Nursing Home Whistleblowers, Amici Curiae Filed with U. S. District Court, 1990 (Box 6 (4-Subject Files), Folder 24)
    - NYAHSA (New York Association of Homes & Services for the Aging), "A Proposal to Reform Medicaid Eligibility for Long Term Care", 1992-1993 (Box 6 (4-Subject Files), Folder 25)
    - NYAHSA Report and Information on Long-Term Care Reform, 1993 (Box 6 (4-Subject Files), Folder 26)
    - NYPHRM V (New York Prospective Hospital Reimbursement Methodology), Briefing Papers and Analysis, 1993 (Box 6 (4-Subject Files), Folder 27)
    - NYPHRM V, Recommendations, 1993 (Box 6 (4-Subject Files), Folder 28)
    - NYS Assembly Committee on Long-Term Care Insurance, 1989-1990 (Box 6 (4-Subject Files), Folder 29)
    - NYS Department of Health Codes Committee, 1996 (Box 6 (4-Subject Files), Folder 30)
    - NYS Department of Health Response to Proposed Cemetery Legislation, Bills S.7455, S.7201, and A.10300, 1994 (Box 6 (4-Subject Files), Folder 31)
    - NYS Legislation, Access to Long-Term Care, Bills S.4674/A.7958, 1993-1994 (Box 6 (4-Subject Files), Folder 32)
    - NYS Legislation, Children's Health Insurance Reform Program, Support Material, 1993 (Box 6 (4-Subject Files), Folder 33)
    - NYS Legislation, Criminal Medical Fraud Bill 4689-A, 1993 (Box 6 (4-Subject Files), Folder 34)
    - NYS Legislation, Health Services Review Bill A.11061, 1992 (Box 6 (4-Subject Files), Folder 35)
    - NYS Legislation, Hearing Aid Industry Bill S.5588B, 1994 (Box 6 (4-Subject Files), Folder 36)
    - NYS Legislation, Hospice Bills S.4201, S.4298, and S.3950-A, 1995 (Box 6 (4-Subject Files), Folder 37)
    - NYS Legislation, Hospital Visitation Bill S.5747, Support Memo, 1994 (Box 6 (4-Subject Files), Folder 38)
    - NYS Legislation, Immunization Bills A.10920./S. 7802, 1994 (Box 6 (4-Subject Files), Folder 39)
    - NYS Legislation, Licensing of Dieticians, Bills A.1578 and #3476, 1985-1989 (Box 6 (4-Subject Files), Folder 40)
    - NYS Legislation, Life Care Communities, Bill S.6327, 1994 (Box 6 (4-Subject Files), Folder 41)
    - NYS Legislation, Long-Term Care Bill A.2713, 1995 (Box 6 (4-Subject Files), Folder 42)
    - NYS Legislation, Patient Abuse/Fraud Bills 7452-A and S.5223, 1989-1990 (Box 6 (4-Subject Files), Folder 43)
    - NYS Legislation, Pet Therapy Bill S.4232, 1995 (Box 6 (4-Subject Files), Folder 44)
    - NYS Legislation, Prescription Drug Prices Bill A.9894/S.7380, 1994 (Box 6 (4-Subject Files), Folder 45)
    - NYS Legislation, Surrogate Bill A.7166, 1994 (Box 6 (4-Subject Files), Folder 46)
    - NYS Legislation, Surrogate Bill A.7166 and Governor's Program Bill #69R, 1994 (Box 6 (4-Subject Files), Folder 47)
    - NYS Legislation, Surrogate Bill A.7166, Statements of Support, 1994 (Box 6 (4-Subject Files), Folder 48)
    - NYS Legislative Reports, 1992-1993 (Box 6 (4-Subject Files), Folder 49)
    - NYS Medical Leave Legislation, Coalition Meeting Material, 1991 (Box 6 (4-Subject Files), Folder 50)
    - NYS Rural Health Coalition, Comparative Analysis of NYPHRM Legislation, 1993 (Box 6 (4-Subject Files), Folder 51)
    - NYS Senate Health Committee Managed Care Hearings, 1995 (Box 6 (4-Subject Files), Folder 52)
    - PASCAS (Personal and Supportive Care Assessment System) Guidelines, Undated (Box 7 (4-Subject Files), Folder 1)
    - Patient Advocacy Project Report, 1989 (Box 7 (4-Subject Files), Folder 2)
    - Patients' Bill of Rights, 1986 (Box 7 (4-Subject Files), Folder 3)
    - Pepper Commission Report on Affordable Health Care, 1990 (Box 7 (4-Subject Files), Folder 4)
    - PPS (Prospective Payment System) and DRG (Diagnosis Related Groups) Information, 1984-1989 (Box 7 (4-Subject Files), Folder 5)
    - PPS and DRG Information, 1989-1990 (Box 7 (4-Subject Files), Folder 6)
    - Primary Care Initiative, 1990 (Box 7 (4-Subject Files), Folder 7)
    - Primary Care Legislation Issues, 1992 (Box 7 (4-Subject Files), Folder 8)
    - PRO (Peer Review Organization) Appeals Data, 1987 (Box 7 (4-Subject Files), Folder 9)
    - PRO Contract Negotiations, 1989 (Box 7 (4-Subject Files), Folder 10)
    - PRO Guidelines, 1985-1986 (Box 7 (4-Subject Files), Folder 11)
    - PRO Information and Procedures, 1984-1986 (Box 7 (4-Subject Files), Folder 12)
    - PRO Information and Procedures, 1987-1989 (Box 7 (4-Subject Files), Folder 13)
    - PRO Liaison Committee Report, 1989 (Box 7 (4-Subject Files), Folder 14)
    - PRO News, 1987-1988 (Box 7 (4-Subject Files), Folder 15)
    - PRO Report, 1986 (Box 7 (4-Subject Files), Folder 16)
    - PRO Report, 1990 (Box 7 (4-Subject Files), Folder 17)
    - Proposal for Geriatric Medical Education, Undated (Box 7 (4-Subject Files), Folder 18)
    - Public Citizen Health Research Correspondence, 1993 (Box 7 (4-Subject Files), Folder 19)
    - Right to Die Campaign, 1990 (Box 7 (4-Subject Files), Folder 20)
    - RUGs (Resource Utilization Groups), 1986-1990 (Box 7 (4-Subject Files), Folder 21)
    - RUGs III: Resource Utilization Groups for Nursing Homes, 1994 (Box 7 (4-Subject Files), Folder 22)
    - SENSES (Statewide Emergency Network for Social and Economic Security) Report on Health Care Coverage for the Uninsured, 1991-1993 (Box 7 (4-Subject Files), Folder 23)
    - Single-Payer Plan Support Information, 1994 (Box 7 (4-Subject Files), Folder 24)
    - SOFA (State Office For the Aging) Expanded In-Home Services, 1986 (Box 7 (4-Subject Files), Folder 25)
    - State Hospital Association Telephone Contact Guidelines, 1987 (Box 7 (4-Subject Files), Folder 26)
    - Telephone Survey on Emergency Room Care, 1988 (Box 7 (4-Subject Files), Folder 27)
    - Testimony Before Assembly Committees, 1993 (Box 7 (4-Subject Files), Folder 28)
    - Testimony Before Governor's Health Care Advisory Board, 1993 (Box 7 (4-Subject Files), Folder 29)
    - Testimony Before State Hospital Review and Planning Council, 1987 (Box 7 (4-Subject Files), Folder 30)
    - Testimonies, Hearings on Medicaid and Health Care Reform, 1990-1992 (Box 7 (4-Subject Files), Folder 31)
    - Testimonies, Welfare Reform, Before NYS Senate Standing Committee on Social Services, 1995 (Box 7 (4-Subject Files), Folder 32)
    - Universal New York Health Care (UNYCARE), 1989-1991 (Box 7 (4-Subject Files), Folder 33)
    - Vermont Medicare Legislation, 1987; 1990 (Box 7 (4-Subject Files), Folder 34)
  - Senior Advocacy, 1974-1979; 1984-1999; 4.2; 2.39 cubic ft.
    Files include material on a variety of issues important to New York seniors in the areas of law, taxes, independent living and in-home care, elder abuse, the Right to Die Campaign, age discrimination and continuing education. NYSSAC's work with other groups such as the Capital Area Consortium on Aging and Disability, the Citizens' Utility Board and the State Office of the Aging's Hunger Action Network are documented in files on conferences, workshops and meetings. Included are testimonies given on major issues before legislative bodies, a memorial booklet for activist Rose Kryzak containing a tribute from Governor Mario Cuomo, and various correspondence.
    - AARP Statements and Events, 1995 (Box 1 (4-Subject Files), Folder 1)
    - Ad Hoc Coalition for the Aging, 1994-1995 (Box 1 (4-Subject Files), Folder 2)
    - Advocate Groups for Seniors, 1992 (Box 1 (4-Subject Files), Folder 3)
    - Age Discrimination, NYS Office for the Aging Report, 1990 (Box 1 (4-Subject Files), Folder 4)
    - Area Agencies for Aging, Directories, 1995 (Box 1 (4-Subject Files), Folder 5)
    - Assembly Committee on Aging Schedule, 1989 (Box 1 (4-Subject Files), Folder 6)
    - Attorney General Pamphlet "Helping Seniors", Undated (Box 1 (4-Subject Files), Folder 7)
    - Bad Debt and Charity Need, Statistics, 1984-1996 (Box 1 (4-Subject Files), Folder 8)
    - Balanced Budget Amendments, 1997 (Box 1 (4-Subject Files), Folder 9)
    - Bar Association Collaboration on Legislation, 1989 (Box 1 (4-Subject Files), Folder 10)
    - Brookdale Center Advocacy Assistance Training, 1979 (Box 1 (4-Subject Files), Folder 11)
    - Budget, Impact on Elder Care, NYS, 1993 (Box 1 (4-Subject Files), Folder 12)
    - Budget Reductions, NYS, 1991-1992 (Box 1 (4-Subject Files), Folder 13)
    - Capital Area Consortium on Aging and Disability, 1993 (Box 1 (4-Subject Files), Folder 14)
    - Capital Area Consortium on Aging and Disability, 1994 (Box 1 (4-Subject Files), Folder 15)
    - Center for Community Change Policy Alerts, 1996 (Box 1 (4-Subject Files), Folder 16)
    - Citizen Advocacy Center, 1994 (Box 1 (4-Subject Files), Folder 17)
    - Coalition Building, Workshop, New York Foundation, 1992 (Box 1 (4-Subject Files), Folder 18)
    - College Curricula for Older Adults, by Hope Bagger, 1974 (Box 1 (4-Subject Files), Folder 19)
    - Congressional Election Action, 1998 (Box 1 (4-Subject Files), Folder 20)
    - Consortium for the Aging, 1992 (Box 1 (4-Subject Files), Folder 21)
    - CSE (Community Services for the Elderly), 1993 (Box 1 (4-Subject Files), Folder 22)
    - CSE Testimony, 1991 (Box 1 (4-Subject Files), Folder 23)
    - CUB (Citizen's Utility Board) Incorporation, 1991 (Box 1 (4-Subject Files), Folder 24)
    - Domestic Partnerships Law, 1991 (Box 1 (4-Subject Files), Folder 25)
    - Earned Income Tax Credit Information, 1993 (Box 1 (4-Subject Files), Folder 26)
    - EISEP (Expanding In-Home Services for the Elderly Program), 1989 (Box 1 (4-Subject Files), Folder 27)
    - Elder Abuse Bills, S.7012 and Departmental Bill # 673, SOFA, 1994 (Box 1 (4-Subject Files), Folder 28)
    - Elder Abuse Conference, 1992 (Box 1 (4-Subject Files), Folder 29)
    - Elderline, Independent Living, 1974; 1990 (Box 1 (4-Subject Files), Folder 30)
    - Executive Budget Welfare Presentation, NYS Departments of Social Services and Labor, 1996-1997 (Box 1 (4-Subject Files), Folder 31)
    - Federal Welfare Reform, Newsletters and News Clippings, 1996 (Box 1 (4-Subject Files), Folder 32)
    - Federal Welfare Reform, Reports, 1996 (Box 1 (4-Subject Files), Folder 33)
    - Federal Welfare Reform, Source Material, 1996 (Box 1 (4-Subject Files), Folder 34)
    - Fiscal Policy Institute Fair Taxes Campaign, 1991 (Box 1 (4-Subject Files), Folder 35)
    - Governor Carey's Task Force on Social Security, 1981 (Box 1 (4-Subject Files), Folder 36)
    - Governor Cuomo's Press Releases, 1991 (Box 1 (4-Subject Files), Folder 37)
    - Hart, Gary, Support Information, 1984 (Box 1 (4-Subject Files), Folder 38)
    - Hunger Action Network, 1990 (Box 1 (4-Subject Files), Folder 39)
    - Income Distribution Statistics, 1988-1990 (Box 1 (4-Subject Files), Folder 40)
    - Innovative Resources Group, Non-Profit Marketing, 1994 (Box 1 (4-Subject Files), Folder 41)
    - Intergenerational Lobby Day, 1995 (Box 1 (4-Subject Files), Folder 42)
    - Jesuit Volunteer Corps, 1986 (Box 1 (4-Subject Files), Folder 43)
    - Job Training Partnership Act, 1989 (Box 1 (4-Subject Files), Folder 44)
    - Kryzak, Rose, Essays About, 1976-1986 (Box 1 (4-Subject Files), Folder 45)
    - Kryzak, Rose, Memorial Tribute, 1999 (Box 1 (4-Subject Files), Folder 46)
    - Labor Issues, 1992 (Box 1 (4-Subject Files), Folder 47)
    - Legal Services Programs, Undated (Box 1 (4-Subject Files), Folder 48)
    - Limited Liability Legislation, 1993 (Box 1 (4-Subject Files), Folder 49)
    - Massachusetts Senior Action Council, 1985 (Box 1 (4-Subject Files), Folder 50)
    - Medicaid Service Changes, NYS Budget, 1995 (Box 1 (4-Subject Files), Folder 51)
    - Miscellaneous, 1988-1989 (Box 1 (4-Subject Files), Folder 52)
    - Non-Profit Resource Center Meeting, 1994 (Box 1 (4-Subject Files), Folder 53)
    - NYS Assembly Energy Committee Proposals, 1994 (Box 1 (4-Subject Files), Folder 54)
    - NYS Government Budget Memo Packet, 1996 (Box 1 (4-Subject Files), Folder 55)
    - NYS Government Fiscal Outlook, 1996-1997 (Box 1 (4-Subject Files), Folder 56)
    - NYS Legislation, Information, 1985-1987 (Box 1 (4-Subject Files), Folder 57)
    - NYS Legislation, Information, 1988 (Box 1 (4-Subject Files), Folder 58)
    - NYS Legislation, Materials, 1991 (Box 1 (4-Subject Files), Folder 59)
    - NYS Legislation, Materials, 1992 (Box 2 (4-Subject Files), Folder 1)
    - NYS Legislation, Materials, 1993 (Box 2 (4-Subject Files), Folder 2)
    - NYS Legislation on Aging, Memos, 1995-1996 (Box 2 (4-Subject Files), Folder 3)
    - NYS Legislation on Aging, Memos, 1997-1998 (Box 2 (4-Subject Files), Folder 4a-b)
    - NYS Legislation, Real Estate Advisory Committee, 1993-1994 (Box 2 (4-Subject Files), Folder 5)
    - NYS Legislation, Senior Citizens' Pets in Housing, Bill S.819, 1989 (Box 2 (4-Subject Files), Folder 6)
    - NYS Legislation, Weatherization Funds, Bill S.6066, 1992 (Box 2 (4-Subject Files), Folder 7)
    - NYS Legislative Action Letters, 1990 (Box 2 (4-Subject Files), Folder 8)
    - NYS Legislative Newsletter on the Elderly, 1991 (Box 2 (4-Subject Files), Folder 9)
    - NYS Office for the Aging Advisory Committee, 1996 (Box 2 (4-Subject Files), Folder 10)
    - NYS Office for the Aging, (SOFA) Legislative Memos, 1987 (Box 2 (4-Subject Files), Folder 11)
    - NYS Office for the Aging, Legislative Memos, 1990 (Box 2 (4-Subject Files), Folder 12)
    - NYS Office for the Aging, Legislative Memos, 1992 (Box 2 (4-Subject Files), Folder 13)
    - NYS Senate Legislative Bills on Aging, 1995-1996 (Box 2 (4-Subject Files), Folder 14)
    - NYS Senate Legislative Bills on Aging, 1997 (Box 2 (4-Subject Files), Folder 15)
    - NYS Welfare Reform, 1995-1996 (Box 2 (4-Subject Files), Folder 16)
    - NYS Welfare, Regulatory Reform, 1995 (Box 2 (4-Subject Files), Folder 17)
    - NYSSAC (New York StateWide Senior Action Council) Coalition vs. Executive Order # 20, Lawsuit, 1996 (Box 2 (4-Subject Files), Folder 18)
    - NYSSAC Convention, 1993 (Box 2 (4-Subject Files), Folder 19)
    - NYSSAC Convention Materials, 1995 (Box 2 (4-Subject Files), Folder 20)
    - NYSSAC Convention Materials, 1996 (Box 2 (4-Subject Files), Folder 21)
    - NYSSAC Convention Materials, 1996-1997 (Box 2 (4-Subject Files), Folder 22)
    - NYSSAC Legislative Strategies and Priorities, 1973-1982 (Box 2 (4-Subject Files), Folder 23)
    - Older Americans Act, 1977-1982 (Box 2 (4-Subject Files), Folder 24)
    - Petitions Against Senate Bill S.1100, Undated (Box 2 (4-Subject Files), Folder 25)
    - Regional Media Contacts, Undated (Box 2 (4-Subject Files), Folder 26)
    - Rent Control, 1997 (Box 2 (4-Subject Files), Folder 27)
    - Retired Senior Volunteer Program (RSVP), 1986 (Box 2 (4-Subject Files), Folder 28)
    - Reverse Mortgage Legislation, 1994 (Box 2 (4-Subject Files), Folder 29)
    - Robin Hood Coalition for Fair State Taxes, 1992 (Box 2 (4-Subject Files), Folder 30)
    - Securities Private Enforcement Reform Act, H.R. 417 and Private Securities Litigation Reform Act, S.1976, 1994 (Box 2 (4-Subject Files), Folder 31)
    - Senior Citizen's Handbook, 1988 (Box 2 (4-Subject Files), Folder 32)
    - Senior Companion Project, 1992 (Box 2 (4-Subject Files), Folder 33)
    - Senior Companion Project, 1993 (Box 2 (4-Subject Files), Folder 34)
    - Senior Service Luncheon, 1993 (Box 2 (4-Subject Files), Folder 35)
    - Seniors for Adequate Social Security Newsletter, 1977-1984 (Box 2 (4-Subject Files), Folder 36)
    - SENSES (Statewide Emergency Network for Social and Economic Security) Board of Directors' Meetings, 1991-1993 (Box 2 (4-Subject Files), Folder 37)
    - SENSES Board of Directors' Meetings, 1994-1995 (Box 2 (4-Subject Files), Folder 38)
    - SENSES Board of Directors' Retreat, 1993 (Box 2 (4-Subject Files), Folder 39)
    - SENSES Personnel Committee, 1992 (Box 2 (4-Subject Files), Folder 40)
    - SENSES Proposals for Counter Budget, 1993-1994 (Box 2 (4-Subject Files), Folder 41)
    - Social Security "Notch", Undated (Box 3 (4-Subject Files), Folder 1)
    - SSI (Supplemental Security Income) Action Letters, 1992 (Box 3 (4-Subject Files), Folder 2)
    - SSI Advocacy Group, 1988-1991 (Box 3 (4-Subject Files), Folder 3)
    - SSI Background, 1988-1989 (Box 3 (4-Subject Files), Folder 4)
    - SSI Conference, 1989 (Box 3 (4-Subject Files), Folder 5)
    - SSI Materials, 1985; 1988 (Box 3 (4-Subject Files), Folder 6)
    - SSI Outreach Program, Proposal, 1988-1989 (Box 3 (4-Subject Files), Folder 7)
    - SSI Outreach Program, 1991 (Box 3 (4-Subject Files), Folder 8)
    - SSI Position Paper, 1990 (Box 3 (4-Subject Files), Folder 9)
    - State Budget File, 1992 (Box 3 (4-Subject Files), Folder 10)
    - State Communities Aid Association, 1991 (Box 3 (4-Subject Files), Folder 11)
    - State Constitutional Convention Proposal, 1996 (Box 3 (4-Subject Files), Folder 12)
    - State Programs for the Aging, 1989 (Box 3 (4-Subject Files), Folder 13)
    - StateWide Platform, 1996 (Box 3 (4-Subject Files), Folder 14)
    - Statewide Youth Advocacy (SYA), 1991-1995 (Box 3 (4-Subject Files), Folder 15)
    - Student Association of the State University (SASU) response to the Governor's Budget, 1995 (Box 3 (4-Subject Files), Folder 16)
    - Tax Cut Opposition, 1995 (Box 3 (4-Subject Files), Folder 17)
    - Testimony Before Subcommittee on Aging, by Bonnie Ray, 1986 (Box 3 (4-Subject Files), Folder 18)
    - Testimony on Banking Bill by Greg Olsen, Public Hearing, 1994 (Box 3 (4-Subject Files), Folder 19)
    - TRIAD-Police Relations, Orange County, NY case, 1995-1996 (Box 3 (4-Subject Files), Folder 20)
    - TRIAD Program, Anti-Crime Bill S-4540-A / A-6706-A, 1993-1995 (Box 3 (4-Subject Files), Folder 21)
    - University at Buffalo, State University of New York, Research Agreement, 1989 (Box 3 (4-Subject Files), Folder 22)
    - University at Buffalo, State University of New York, Research Project, 1989 (Box 3 (4-Subject Files), Folder 23)
    - Violent Crime Initiative, 1995 (Box 3 (4-Subject Files), Folder 24)
    - Women's Issues, 1993 (Box 3 (4-Subject Files), Folder 25)
  - Consumer Fraud, 1988-1994; 4.3; 0.25 cubic ft.